(
"ai_sub_version": "3.5.1",
"generated_at": "2026-08-07T05:20:47.813958",
"lyrics_prompt_version": 9,
"subtitles_prompt_version": 18,
"complete": true,
"max_retries_exceeded": false,
"any_pending": false,
"settings": (
"ai": (
"model": null,
"model_subtitles": "google-gla:gemini-3.5-flash-lite",
"model_lyrics": "google-gla:gemini-3.5-flash-lite",
"rpm": 4,
"tpm": 250000,
"google": (
"file_cache_ttl": 10,
"use_files_api": true,
"max_storage_gb": 18.0
),
"search": (
"qps": 0.3,
"max_length": 4096,
"web_search_tool": "langsearch",
"timeout": 60.0,
"retries": 3,
"min_wait_seconds": 1.0,
"max_wait_seconds": 10.0,
"multiplier": 2.0
),
"validation_buffer_ms": 2000,
"verification_gap_seconds": 60,
"gap_verification_retries": 1,
"gap_verification_ignore_start": true,
"gap_verification_ignore_end": true
),
"split": (
"max_seconds": 300,
"re_encode": (
"enabled": false,
"fps": 1.0,
"height": 360,
"bitrate_kb": 35,
"threshold_mb": 20,
"duration_tolerance_ms": 100,
"encoder": null
),
"start_offset_min": 0
"thread": (
"uploads": 4,
"re_encode": 2,
"lyrics": 4,
"subtitles": 4
),
"retry": (
"per_run": 5,
"max_runs": 3,
"multiplier": 2.0,
"min_wait_seconds": 30.0,
"max_wait_seconds": 300
),
"log": (
"level": "info",
"timestamps": true,
"scrub": false,
"progress_bars": true,
"progress_bar_width": 80,
"progress_bar_refresh_seconds": 1.0
)
Sing out boldly again,
continuing this odyssey.
We'll start this new refrain brimming with memories!
And when the clouded skies become bright, let's reunite!
Ready? Set? Stream! It's showtime, baby!
I would say.
Today's broadcast on slight delay... rubbing out the scuff,
is it really enough?
Stuck on buffering endlessly, why?!
Take it easy, what have we learned?
Start a fire in their hearts when the PC burns!
Upbeat, focus on a quick fix!
Teach new dogs all of our old tricks!
Still going stronger than ever, and never saying die!
And I'm aware it's ironic, but where's the freaking lie?
Dreamers to streamers to entertainers to senpai!
Spanning new dimensions,
we can bring another mystery to light!
Planning our ascension, dancing in flight, we ignite!
Through this world and beyond,
our distant dreams have brought us here.
A strong, unyielding bond,
guiding us endlessly, will bring us moments that we hold dear.
Time rushes on; and though these winds may scatter us,
we'll keep this promise: when the moment's finally right,
we'll always find a way to reunite!
I'm diving in again, now it's time to sink or swim!
Let's try the deeper end, but could you hold my fin?
Vibing with everyone, let's kick back and ponder puns!
Tako time anytime, let's get cozy and have fun!
And I know that it's morbid, years come and go,
I'll still pretend that I've got this killin' and assorted list,
Listen, I wanna look cool, but I keep on trippin' and fallin',
guess I'll keep playin' the fool to hold up the cover, callin' yatta yatta
Countless moments lead us to this day,
Triumph and sorrow, hope for tomorrow,
We'll always find our way, trouble may... come what may!
In every universe, we were always meant to meet.
A little boundless search, we will never know defeat!
My wings will guide your hands as the fateful days go by,
we will cut a path through a never-ending sky!
Drawing us together,
I can sense another wish is coming true.
Each typhoon we weather strengthens our crew, me and you.
Say it again, the clouded skies give way to clear,
We'll start this new refrain, brimming with memories, another story starting right here!
We'll keep forging ahead, to make a saga all our own,
Whichever paths we tread, steadily journeying, we know we're never really alone—
if we believe, wherever fate may find us,
our love will find us, every epic chapter we write
will set us on the path to reunite!
Take off and fly, the longer we wait,
the stronger it makes us as we fight every fate,
strength to finally defeat this journey a thousand years to meet...
Song in snow, enchanted by rhyme,
painted in wishes, granted by time,
our longest hopes, connecting, yet those...
feel like echoes of ages gone by!
Made a splash, but found I'm not free,
a fish out of water, bound to the sea,
yet a reckless high tide brought you right by my side,
I bet this moment's a wave we can ride!
Connecting songs across the sky!
Take off and fly, the longer we wait, the stronger it makes us as we fight every fate,
strength to finally defeat this journey a thousand years to meet...
Witness the fire in our minds, burning inside, rising again from the ashes,
every bruise, any scratches make us feel more alive!
We never give up, never giving in, no matter what's ahead, instead we'll crush our worries aside!
If there's no world for us to touch or to see, we'll make it ourselves and make memories!
There ain't a mystery our brains cannot solve, we just shine brighter, grow tighter, evolve!
Connecting songs across that wall!
Take off and fly, the longer we wait, the stronger it makes us as we fight every fate,
strength to finally defeat this journey a thousand years to meet...
At the end of this world, where's our fighting chance?
seek out a happy end for me , my friends ,
Seek out a happy end for me, my friends,
and those who 've loved us up until now
and those who've loved us up until now.
I wanna see your smile
find my way to you somehow
take off and fly , the longer we wait ,
Take off and fly, the longer we wait,
the stronger it makes us as we fight every fate
strength to finally defeat this journey a thousand years to meet ...
Strength to finally defeat this journey a thousand years to meet...
let 's try ! it can't be denied ,
Let's try! It can't be denied,
the wish in my heart is you right here by my side
strength is all that we 'll need , I won't wait a thousand years to meet ...
Strength is all that we'll need, I won't wait a thousand years to meet...
Yeah, good, but everybody knows, right?
Yeah, yeah, but once again,
Hi guys! We're off to a flying start already, but...
to properly kick things off, welcome everybody to Hololive English Myth's 4th anniversary live!
The show goes on! Welcome everybody!
Yeah, well, let's start off with a round of introductions. So, who'll be our first?
Oh, oh. Okay, it'll be me. Um, all right.
Kika-Kikihiki, hello everybody, I'm Takanashi Kiara from Hololive English Myth, you'll hear that a lot today.
So, who is next?
Zombie, zombie, doo. Oh no, zombie? Don't be scared, keep 'em coming, keep 'em coming!
Water? Oh, meat? Okay.
Mina-san! Hi. I think you guys maybe know who I am. My name is Mori Calliope from Hololive English Myth. I am a virtual singer, artist, creator. I stream, I play games too.
Nice to meet you, if we have already met, if we haven't, if we have... Hi. Someone take the mic away from me!
So bad at these, I'm always so bad. Someone else do it.
Who's next? Ame? Perhaps. Okay, I'm Amelia Watson, number one detective from Hololive English!
And last but not least... Wah! Good morning, afternoon, evening, everyone!
I'm Ninomae Ina'nis from... well, I'll say Hololive English...
Hololive English, and together we are Hololive English -Myth-!
Yay! See, I told you, you'll hear it a lot.
So, we've our introductions out of the way. Feast your eyes on the venue we have today!
A brand new stage made for Myth's 4th anniversary! Our songs, our songs are everywhere, our originals!
Fire! Oh, yeah. That's pretty high.
Some Valentine stuff, cute. Oh, yeah, yeah, we're stars.
So, I'm sure it's obvious, right everybody? We've got full divine and exquisite...
for the show goes on. Can you guess what the theme is? Anybody? Anybody?
Tropical island vacation!
What? Underwater sea adventure!
Are you for real? What? You asked for it.
It's definitely that one. I think so.
Okay. No, I don't think they'll have good answers either. So, let's do bone heads. Drumroll, though, come on, drumroll! It's Broadway!
Okay. No, I don't think they'll have good answers either. So... drumroll, though, come on, drumroll! It's Broadway!
Yeah. And that's not just, you know, a Broadway, it's also a red carpet!
Do you really like good fashion, baby? Yeah, yeah, we got it. Fashion, baby.
Oh, yeah, we got it! Nice, that's what I really wanted to do. Thanks. Okay, that's pretty cool, too.
So, along with the stunning backdrop, you guys, I hope you will enjoy our grand performance, but it's not just any live concert, we've got a fun surprise waiting for them, don't be late.
I'm a V... I'm a V...
We have a surprise?
Yeah.
Did you forget already, Ina?
Didn't hear it.
I forgot the surprise!
I mean, it's not a surprise if we know about it.
Play along, play along.
We have a surprise, guys! Yay!
Yeah, we know about it already.
If you keep on watching until the end, you will indeed find out.
So in the meantime, everybody, I ask you to use the hashtag at the top right of your screen...
Where should they post the screenshots?
My fridge!
Post your fridge?
Post them on X, formerly known as Twitter.
Yeah. Not the refrigerator.
Spelling bee ladies.
Everybody, Hololive English Myth now presents our fourth anniversary live.
The show goes on in Shibuya!
That's right, I'm not just a detective!
I'm a time traveler!
Look at this!
When we first met,
I wonder what you'd think of me.
The image was set,
it was a perfect narrative.
But as time went by, I forgot to hide
the laughs that came so naturally.
Through lows and highs, I'd wonder why
I ever thought you would leave.
Now no matter where or when we are,
I know it's you I can count on.
Magical, mythical,
nothing can stop us now!
Let's go!
Chikutaku, where'd the time go?
Wakuwaku, how should I know
why it seems when you're here with me
the clock won't stop spinning?
Wapu, wapu, wapu, wapu,
Doki doki, hearts beat faster,
Tomodachi, friends forever,
it's clear to see
that this mystery was solved immediately.
時空の歪み
A distortion in space-time.
It's been so long
since I laughed so hard I cried.
Now you came along,
it happens almost every time
that I hear your voice, I'm left no choice
but to let you know what you mean to me.
Spiraling, time skipping
through treasured memories.
Now no matter where or when we're from,
our friendship's elementary.
Case closed, now you know,
nothing can stop us now!
Let's go!
Chikutaku, where'd the time go?
Wakuwaku, how should I know
why it seems when you're here with me
the clock won't stop spinning?
Wapu, wapu, wapu, wapu,
Doki doki, hearts beat faster,
Tomodachi, friends forever,
it's clear to see
that this mystery was solved immediately.
時空の歪み
A distortion in space-time.
Though each day, we're older,
what the future holds is
not, not, not for us to know yet.
It's gone, gone, gone before we know it,
so let's solve the question.
We can make each second
chikutaku, last forever,
wakuwaku, it's now or never!
Chikutaku, where'd the time go?
Wakuwaku, how should I know
why it seems when you're here with me
the clock won't stop spinning?
Wapu, wapu, wapu, wapu,
Doki doki, hearts beat faster,
Tomodachi, friends forever,
it's clear to see
that this mystery was solved immediately.
時空の歪み
A distortion in space-time.
That's right, I'm not just a detective!
I'm a time traveler!
Look at this!
that's right, i'm not just a detective!
i'm a time traveler!
watch this!
when we first met I wonder what you'd think of me
the image was set it was a perfect narrative
but as time went by i forgot to hide
the laughs that came so naturally
through lows and highs i'd wonder why
i ever thought you would leave
now no matter where or when we are i know it's you i can count on
magical
mythical
nothing can stop us now! let's go!
chikutaku where'd the time go?
waku waku how should i know why it seems
when you're here with me the clock won't stop spinning?
wapu wapu wapu wapu
doki doki hearts beat faster
tomodachi friends forever
it's clear to see that this mystery was solved immediately
jiku no yugami
it's been so long
since i laughed so hard i cried
now you came along
it happens almost every time
that i hear your voice i'm left no choice
but to let you know what you mean to me
spiraling time skipping through treasured memories
now no matter where or when we're from our friendship's elementary
case closed now you know
nothing can stop us now! let's go!
chikutaku where'd the time go?
waku waku how should i know why it seems
when you're here with me the clock won't stop spinning?
wapu wapu wapu wapu
doki doki hearts beat faster
tomodachi friends forever
it's clear to see that this mystery was solved immediately
jiku no yugami
though each day we're older what the future holds is
not not not for us to know yet it's gone gone gone before we know it
so let's solve the question we can make each second
chikutaku last forever
waku waku it's now or never!
chikutaku where'd the time go?
waku waku how should i know why it seems
when you're here with me the clock won't stop spinning?
wapu wapu wapu wapu
doki doki hearts beat faster
tomodachi friends forever
it's clear to see that this mystery was solved immediately
jiku no yugami
that's right i'm not just a detective!
i'm a time traveler!
look at this!
εκ λόγου άλλος
One word brings another
εκβαίνει λόγος
My reflection in the water
水面に映る自分と言った
Says to me
「ああ、私は悪いサメです」
"Oh my god, you're such a bad shark"
ずっと恐れていた、赤く光るその目
Her terrifying gaze, her glowing red eyes
海の色、暗闇に消えていく
Sink into the void at the bottom of the sea
どうして
Why do you cry?
泣くのか
Begin to fall
欲しいものなら全部手に入れた
I gave you everything you craved
教えて
Tell me if
私は
I can ever be
望んでいた私になれたかな
The me you wanted me to be
嘘はつけないでも本当じゃない
No lies, but no truths either
本音は言わない方が楽しくない？
Isn't it easier to never say what you really mean?
いつかは
But someday
どこかで
Somewhere
分かり合える時が来るの？
Will we find someplace to understand each other?
look at this so-called "gem of the sea"
odd and scrawny, you see what i mean?
return to what you know, it ain't much i know, heh, it shows
私はあなたとは違うの
I'm not like you
やめてよ、決めつけはもう大嫌い
Stop it, I hate the way you judge me
理想の姿じゃなくていいのかな
I don't need to conform to any ideals
私らしくあれば、ただわかって欲しいだけよ
I just want to be myself, just want to be understood
heh! 理想通りじゃないくしゃ意味なんてない
Heh! If you don't conform, then why were you even born?
希望も夢すらなくて、辛い、辛い、辛い、辛い
There are no hopes, no dreams, just pain, pain, pain, pain
あなたらしさ、あるのかしら？
Be yourself? Do you even know who you are?
あきらめて楽になろう、さあ
Give it up and just ride the waves, just chill
ずっと追い求められた私なりの答え
I've been searching and searching, and found my own answer
自分には嘘をつきたくないの
I won't lie to myself anymore
ごめんね
I'm sorry
今まで気づけなかったことがあるんだけど
All this time I've been too blind to see
こうしてあなたが
I'm only here this way
いてくれたから今の私がいる
Because of you, because you've been there by my side
過去はいらない？そんなことはない
The past isn't important? That's not true
ここから静かに私を見守っていてね
From here on out, just watch quietly how I live my life
水面に映る自分が言った
My reflection in the water said to me,
「ああ、私は悪い鮫です」
"Oh my god, you're such a bad shark."
ずっと恐れていた赤く光るその目
That glowing red gaze I always feared
海の底暗闇に消えていく
Fades into the abyss of the sea.
どうして (your tired eyes)
Why...
泣くのよ (begin to fall)
Do you cry?
欲しいものなら全部手に入れた
I'll take everything I ever craved.
教えて (your darkest thoughts)
Tell me...
私なら望んでいた私になれたかな
Have I finally become the me I wanted to be?
嘘はつけない でも本当じゃない
No lies, but no truth either.
本音は言わない方が楽じゃない?
Isn't it easier to never say what you really mean?
いつかは (a time and place)
Someday...
どこかで (for darker days) 分かり合える時が来るの?
Somewhere... Will we understand each other?
look at this so-called "gem of the sea"
odd and scrawny, don't you see what i mean?
return to what you know, it ain't much, i know
it shows
Heh, it shows.
私はあなたとは違うの
I'm not like you!
めてよ 決めつけはもう大嫌い (大嫌い)
Stop it, I hate being judged like this!
理想の姿じゃなくていいの
I don't need to fit into any ideals,
私らしくあれば
I just want to be myself,
ただ分かって欲しいだけよ
And finally be understood!
heh ! 理想通りじゃなきゃ意味なんてない
If you don't conform, what's the point of it all?
希望も夢すらなくて 辛い辛い辛い辛い
No hopes, no dreams, just endless pain!
あなたらしさあるのかしら
Be yourself? Do you even know who you are?
あきらめて楽になろう さあ
Just give it up and ride the waves!
ずっと追い求めた私なりの答え
I've searched and found my own answer at last.
自分には嘘はつきたくないのか
I won't lie to myself anymore!
ごめんね (one story ends)
I'm sorry...
今まで (begin again)
All this time...
気づかなかったことがあるんだけど
I was too blind to see.
こうして (while hand-in-hand)
How hand in hand...
あなたが (until the end)
Until the end...
いてくれたから今の私がいる
You've been by my side, and now I'm here.
過去はいらない? そんなことはない
The past isn't important? That's not true!
未来は見えない方がましじゃない
A future you can't see is so much better!
ここから (no matter where)
No matter where...
静かに (watch over me)
Watch over me...
私を見守っていてね
Please watch over me from now on.
so, you think that's all, huh?
just gonna leave like it's nothing?
going without me?
i don't know what you're thinking!
return to the sea
a shark is all you'll ever be
さようなら (our story ends)
Farewell...
ありがとう (begin again)
Thank you...
隠していた私はもういない
I won't hide my true desires anymore.
さようなら (once hand-in-hand)
Farewell...
ありがとう (until the end)
Thank you...
全てを受け入れて生きていくから
I'll accept everything and keep living.
海の底はつまらないけど
The bottom of the sea is a boring place,
あなたのことは忘れないから
But I will never forget about you.
いつでも (no matter where)
No matter when...
どこでも (watch over me)
No matter where...
私らしく生きていこう
I'll live life true to myself.
Time to die, bird!
It's your time to die!
I'm gonna get you, final countdown!
Get over here! Get over here!
You stupid bird!
Dogeza, dogeza, dogeza!
That's what I thought.
I'm sorry. Neal, what did I do?
You guys forget that I am a killer.
Actually, sometimes I forget that I am a killer.
That was fun though!
How did you guys like Reflect?
That was dramatic, right?
Dramatic, yes.
I got to make up for my lack of dancing skills with...
With drama!
You did well!
I don't know.
It was really tough.
It was much harder with the scythe, right?
It is very heavy.
It looks like it's not very heavy, but it actually weighs a ton.
I'm just really strong, you see.
But the way you're dancing around with it is kind of dangerous.
Yeah, sorry about that if I accidentally hit you.
It would mean curtains for you, but...
That's what I secretly want.
So we never reflected together, huh?
We did!
As our duo song.
And what did you do?
I did full color on Guragura.
I love that song so much.
Still unreleased.
Oh, still unreleased.
When is it, Gury-ban?
That was probably the hardest solo choreography I've learned...
Aside from maybe "Gougetters."
That was the hardest, so...
That's good, you have to challenge yourselves.
I was happy to challenge myself to learn that.
I still know the movement, so...
You know, the hip sway is so fun.
Yeah, I can imagine.
What about you? What did you sing?
I did "I'm a Seikyu Takoo."
Well, you know, actually, originally when they were like...
"So we're going to do the Neko Switcheroo,
You're singing whatever who song you want to sing."
And I said, "I'mama, please let me do I'mama! I want to sing Seikyu Takoo!"
And I was like... I was like the first, I think, to shout out.
So I know how much you love that song.
And I loved your bouncy movements to it.
And I like that you changed the lyrics too.
"I'm not just a Phoenix, I'm a tenchou!"
Yeah, something like that.
It was cute.
So desu ne.
And we finished it off with our "Reflect,"
Which I think is made to be, you know, with, to be...
It's a duet after all.
And we make a really good duet.
So there seems to be a theme, right?
Of doing each other's songs.
It seems so. Interesting.
What are your guesses?
Who will do who and like what song?
What you thinkin'?
Not at all.
Okay.
So, maybe your wish'll come true.
Well, it's not over yet, motherfucker.
Zen zen desu ne? Zen zen.
Far from it, right? Far from it.
So, we gotta pump up the energy just a little bit more, you guys!
Keep it going because there's so much more left! Let's enjoy together, or else...
Remember, I'm a killer! Take it seriously, guys!
I'm so scared!
Don't forget that I'm the reaper! I'm crazy! I'll come after you! I promise, I'm crazy.
As you just saw.
Anyway.
Okay, how should we end it?
Get excited! Takamori!
Yeah!
Bye-bye! See you later!
See ya!
漕ぎ出す海に浮かぶ島へ行け 世界変える未来一番のラボで
Head to the island floating in the sea you set sail for, at the number one lab in the future that changes the world!
最高峰の叶える欲望 未来のお宝探し出そう
Let's search out the treasure of the future, fulfilling our highest desires!
現実が壁を壊す発端の奇跡 笑い合えない夢のファンタジー
The miracle that starts reality breaking down walls, a dream fantasy where we can't share a laugh
世界がひっくり返るテクノロジー 考えちゃうラボラトリー
Technology that turns the world upside down, a laboratory to think things through
しゃかりき進め地動説アドラステア 良くも悪くものサテライト
Advance frantically, Adrastea the heliocentric theory, satellites for better or worse
湧き出すアイデア止まらない 忙しすぎて猫の手も借りたい
Ideas welling up endlessly, so busy I'd even borrow a cat's paw
海も波も越えていく海賊を 常識変えていく発明を
Pirates going beyond seas and waves, inventions changing common sense
そんな奴らに憧れ育ち来た
Growing up admiring such rogues,
次は俺らが王になる
next, we'll become kings!
無限の夢 未来の知恵
Endless dreams, future wisdom,
ひらめきを巻き起こせ
stir up inspiration!
無限の夢 未来の知恵
Endless dreams, future wisdom,
過去も世界も飛び越えて
leaping across past and world!
ベガパンク 生み出すよアイディア
Vegapunk, creating ideas,
ベガパンク
Vegapunk!
革命起こここから ベガパンク
Revolution starts here, Vegapunk!
漕ぎ出す海に浮かぶ島へ行け 世界変える未来一番のラボで
Head to the island floating in the sea you set sail for, at the number one lab in the future that changes the world!
最高峰の叶える欲望 未来のお宝探し出そう
Let's search out the treasure of the future, fulfilling our highest desires!
奇跡のアメリカライクアイディアからせーので飛び出せ
A miraculous American-like idea, let's jump out on the count of three!
ファンタスティックジェームズは燃え上がってインサイド
Fantastic James is burning up inside,
リターンだラボラトリー キャストオフオンザシー
returning to the laboratory, cast off on the sea!
トラベイズエントゥーイボルブアンツコンデンスオブマインド アズアンドノレッジピアレンスエックスサテライト
Troubles into evolve into condensed of mind, as and knowledge appearance x satellites
アイディアキャントストップフラッシュアウトソーシンスキンディマイクトユザハンドレッドオンドゥーアイムビジーワーキングイントゥザナイト
Ideas can't stop flashing out so thinking they might...
ファイアキングオブレイズイーストオブシリコンバレーインサーチオブエデュケーション
Fire King of blaze East of Silicon Valley in search of education,
無限の夢 未来の知恵
Endless dreams, future wisdom,
ひらめきを巻き起こせ
stir up inspiration!
無限の夢 未来の知恵
Endless dreams, future wisdom,
過去も世界も飛び越えて
leaping across past and world!
ベガパンク 生み出すよアイディア
Vegapunk, creating ideas,
ベガパンク
Vegapunk!
革命起こここから ベガパンク
Revolution starts here, Vegapunk!
行くこと鄙けりゃ振りかざす正義 世界守り隠んだの大義
Heading out and brandishing justice, defending the world is our grand cause!
秘密めぐる怪しき試練 過去の記憶に隠された狂気
Mysteries and suspicious trials, madness hidden in past memories,
真実を告げな雪奇効
telling the truth, telling the bitter snow!
なぞに見出されその夢のエネルギー
Finding out the energy of that dream mysteriously,
天才が魅せる世界のカタチ どこへ行こう未来の島へヘッド
the shape of the world shown by a genius, where should we go, head to the island of the future!
oh no ~ fell into the abyss unknown,
Oh no... fell into the abyss unknown,
left me bleedin' , heartless all alone
left me bleeding out, heartless all alone
no control a-yo a-yo
don'tcha dare apologize
turn my back and felt a cold knife
listen up cause here 's some advice - uh
listen up 'cause here's some advice - uh
you outta time way outta line
you're outta time, way outta line
It's taking over, like a renegade
Eye for an eye, I'll make you cry
Tearing it down, do just what I wanna
Keep calling me a sinner
Now ya think so
Chimeri-eri-eri-a
Got me twisted
Such a misfit
Taking the crown, now you're calling me king, you're gonna hear 'em all sing
Now sing it
Chimeri-eri-eri-a
Louder like that
Chimeri-eri-eri-a, make 'em all: ah
Don't back it up, don't back it up, keep that aim, I got thoughts that will drive you insane
Come over if you like, we'll have a lot of fun,
but I got a lot of bite
I do what I want, make sure you don't forget it,
an army on my back, say I'm sick, I'm just sadistic
Not living in a lie, pariah in the light, I wanna see the way you bleed
It's taking over like a renegade
Eye for an eye, I'll make you cry
Tearing it down, do just what I wanna
Keep calling me a sinner
Now ya think so
Chimeri-eri-eri-a
Got me twisted
Such a misfit
Taking the crown, now you're calling me king, you're gonna hear 'em all sing
Now sing it
Chimeri-eri-eri-a
Louder like that
Chimeri-eri-eri-a, make 'em all: ah
I want it all, so gimme some more, flames burnt me up down into my core
Oh, you wished I'd stay down, but then I just rise, you're not my enemy, baby, you're dead to me
Hear my voices screaming out loud, no doubt, yeah
La-la-la-la-la-la, chimeri-eri-yaya
La-la-la-la-la-la, chimeri-eri-a
Tearing it down, do just what I wanna
Keep calling me a sinner
Now ya think so
Chimeri-eri-eri-a
Got me twisted
Such a misfit
Taking the crown, now you're calling me king, you're gonna hear 'em all sing
Now sing it
Chimeri-eri-eri-a
Louder like that
Chimeri-eri-eri-a, make 'em all: ah
La-la-la-la-la-la, chimeri-eri-a
花が寝る夜 波に映った星
As the flowers rest, and the waves reflect the stars above
うねる月が 足をくすぐる
The waxing moon incites my wanderlust
流れる光に沿って行ってみたら
If I trace its trickles of light,
耳に囁いた 君に届くかな
Will I come to you like you asked me to?
今 手をつないでも 精一杯 抱きしめても
Even with all the hand holding and tight embraces,
空は秋に満ちるんだ
The sky will still turn red, and the leaves will still fall
指先でゆらゆらと その動きが
My fingers reach in longingly
止まった時計の針に踏み込んだ
To get the clock ticking once again
固まった願いさえ 離れた今は
With my wishes frozen in time and long forgotten,
その笑顔を 知ってるよ
your fleeting smile is all I know
光歌う夜 目に映った空 ざわやかな香りがくすぐる
As the moonlight dances on the waves, and my eyes reflect the sky above
足跡を合わせて歩いてみたら
A pleasant scent tickles my fancy,
私を見ていた 君に届くかな ずっと 手をつないでも 君について行ってみても 空は雨に染まるんだ
If I walk in step with the wafting breeze, will I be able to go back to you when you only had eyes for me?
君を呼び出した 声の形が 乾いた色を濡らして
My silent voice calls out your name longingly to return luster to my faded paints
強く叫んだ声が 散らばった今は
With my voice hoarse and long ran dry,
その言葉を 知ってるよ
your fleeting words are all I know
なんとなく 描いた夢
Somehow, drawing a dream...
指でなぞる ひこうき雲
Tracing a contrail with my finger.
背伸びして 届きそうで 届かなくて...
Reaching up on tiptoe, almost touching, yet missing...
小さな手で すくいあげた 君の夢の欠片
The fragments of your dreams that you scooped up with small hands,
何を見てるの 何を想うの
What are you looking at? What are you thinking?
目に見えない想いは こころの中彷徨う
Invisible feelings linger in my heart.
闇を 手探って
Searching the darkness with my hands,
雲の流れを 追いかけて
Chasing the flow of the clouds.
瞳に空映して 風の囁きそっと感じているの
Reflecting the sky in my eyes, feeling the wind softly blowing.
のばした指先よりも ずっと遠く
Farther away than my outstretched fingertips,
瞬く間とけてしまう 虹の橋も 夢時間も
In the blink of an eye, the bridge of rainbows and dream times vanish,
つながった 時をこえて 光放つ
Connected across time, releasing light.
Ah...
We'd run right through those nights
I'll never find my way back to you inside this labyrinth of lights
there was madness in the meaning
never laughless, we were screaming at the top of our lungs to the numbness
this city never died.
I'll fly, no proof,
those heights, I'll never find another chance to say, "hey, thanks for saving my life."
I was hopeless, it was stinging,
running roadless, we were screaming at the top of our lungs to the numbness,
this city never died.
What was the root of it all?
...I couldn't say.
I used to jump and then fall, rugged and cliché.
Would shrug it off without complaint, not a sound.
No use in trying to find friends, 'cause in the end nobody sticks around.
It's when you shoved yourself into a crowded place
that you turned around and found yourself in love in outer space.
Cue the reckless nights, no strings, laughing at our own dreams.
Just what the hell was so funny?
Bark up the wrong tree, stumble, used to falling great heights.
Amidst a concrete jungle, singing 'cause it felt right.
We mixed the ennui and troubles, rhyming our discontent,
and though it's history, I can't forget the time that we spent.
Convinced that this could mean another end exists between real and pretend.
A twisted alter-fiction where I missed my chance, did not ascend, and
disappearing into the mist of "never happened"
is the me that I can never befriend.
I let it go.
Fade in, fade out.
This crazy dream without a direction, floating aimlessly.
There's nothing left back there for me.
Breathe in, but it won't stop the rain from pouring.
We'd run right through those nights,
I'll never find my way back to you inside this labyrinth of lights.
There was madness in the meaning,
never laughless, we were screaming at the top of our lungs to the numbness,
this city never died.
But was there ever a soul inside?
Chasing fireflies between the soaring high-rises,
left a trail behind, defined it "wasted time of our lives."
Silent singer, overworked and underpaid,
thinks an office is a coffin until off is where you're laid.
Yet a thought persists, an optimist who ought to be afraid
saw the "nothing wrong" in writing songs behind the lonely shade.
Is the world a sadder place without the words that you conveyed?
When the ladder fell and shattered every bar that we had played?
Does it matter in the end the sound diminished and decayed?
And your friends grew tired of fantasy, you're wishing they had stayed?
You don't get to say "I miss you," you watched your heroes fade
into the rearview mirror of the villain you portrayed.
Stop the pity party, listen, you don't get to be dismayed.
You don't get to be emotional, feel blessed you got it made.
These the best of years of life because you chose to make a trade.
Recollect the days you hoped and you prayed for this, what is there to miss?
Fade in, fade out.
This hazy dream without a direction, roaming aimlessly.
There's nothing left back there for me.
Pretend it's the end of a made-up story.
I'll fly, no proof,
we'd run right through those nights
i'll never find my way back to you
inside this labyrinth of lights
there was madness in the meaning
never laugh less, we were screaming
at the top of our lungs to the numbness
this city never died
i'll keep waiting
i'll keep waiting for you
waking up now
to my real life
lemme daydream 'til the next flight
Let me daydream 'til the next flight.
drowning so long
i got older
now the crowd's gone
is it over?
one, two, three!
light the floodlights, let's begin.
we'll start stage right and shuffle on in.
it's time for myth, ready to steal the show!
we're jumping with joy, let's go!
curtain's up, so cue the band,
we'll keep on entertaining, hand in hand!
it's our greatest moment yet,
a spectacle they'll never forget!
we're all aglow, party from dusk to dawn,
the show will go on and on!
tell them that we're here to stay and
spread the news from tokyo to broadway!
gleaming
ooh
spotlight
aah, get the gang together, we're boogieing all night
beaming
ooh
so bright
aah, now we're feeling all right!
since the day we met, we've all been going strong
it's been so long, ooh!
and we'll keep moving right along, so...
so keep on dancing, yeah, you bet ain't nothing gonna stop us,
we're a perfect quintet!
in harmony no matter where we go,
it's meant to be, don't you know?
we're gonna feel so alive when it's us five,
ready to put on another show!
there's a ton to celebrate,
the mood is fun and we're feeling great!
from the rafters to the aisles contagious laughter and our biggest smiles!
we'll slay 'em like we always do, make no bones about it!
We'll show 'em like we always do, make no bones about it!
When I'm with you, it's divine, it's exquisite.
On land or in water, we've never been hotter; it feels sublime.
We're friends for all time!
(Come on, listen to the Tentacult and jive with me, gonna shake your feathers here with KFP,)
(Deadbeats keeping rhythm while the Teamates spin, the Chumbuds join right in!)
We're like a work of art, and I'm gonna keep you in my heart.
We'll stick together.
Myth forever!
Symphony of sight and sound turning like a merry-go-round,
(We can get 'em cheering even more! On and on, and encore!)
Dream another dream with me, now it's time to change the key!
Light the floodlights, keep 'em lit, tonight's our night, and we've got a hit!
Get in line beside me now, it's almost time to take another bow!
We'll stay on track, you know that I've got your back!
(I say) Get on the dance floor (Okay!) Hear the applause roar (Each day)
The music will go on and on, and encore!
(Old friends) Wherever you go (New gens) I'm gonna follow
(No ends) The music will go on and on, an endless show!
My legs!
are getting so...
A thousand years!
That was a good time.
Yeah, you guys just listened to Myth's new song, "The Show Goes On!"
What do you think? Pretty exciting, right?
Very exciting! Very exciting!
Yeah, Broadway!
We figured we'd stick with the Broadway theme and make it something like, you know, musical, something that would make everyone on their feet and dance! And we did!
And we did, we did! You'll still get fit too.
So, kinky! Yes, fun! And the title truly encapsulates what we think.
We really want the fun to last forever and Myth-
And to make that happen, all of us in Myth are going to do the best we can, and those are the feelings that were packed nicely into this new song.
Hope you guys will listen to it a lot because it will be on the streaming platforms very soon. So get ready to wear out your speakers!
And also the MV is going to be right after this. We're going right into it, be ready!
But that's not all! Maybe another little surprise... We have merchandise coming out!
For good sports fans, let's go!
Now, we will not show it right now, but it will be shown at the very end of the stream at the ending screen, so stay tuned for that!
So, we don't have much time left... I thought I'd like to hear what you ladies are currently thinking. Who wants to go first?
Oh, me! Me, shark! All right, go shark!
Gura split out of nowhere, I guess. I guess she can do that. That was really good, she was so excited to sing it!
It's showtime, baby! Amelia was really good, right? Thank you so much! It was such a fun time!
Okay! Who else? Maybe you?
Well, it kind of reminded me of when Myth started together in the past and with our journey over a thousand years, and now looking at all these performances into the future...
Future island! We're playing around too much. That was really, oh me! Oh gosh, well I don't know guys.
I feel like we've been through so much together and I'm so happy to be by your side!
You guys don't like my theater moves?
Give me, give me something wholesome, come on.
Fine, fine, fine. I love singing songs that I love with people that I love. That's it. That's all there is to it.
I had a lot of fun with you guys. You guys are the best. And uh, yeah, before it gets too sappy, somebody else take the mic.
I think we're going through everybody, but what did you think? What did you think?
Yeah, well, today I did a little bit of MCing here. I did well, but...
For me, you know, I realized when we joined, our oldest senpais I think were around like four years, right?
Years into the game, and now we're four years in, so...
We're all old. We're like really proper senpais now.
And everybody, you got to respect us, pay the senpai tax.
Yeah, pay up.
So all of these four years, hopefully more, and you know, I want to make more memories. This was definitely a big nice memory.
So the show must go on. The show goes on indeed, just like the title. We're going to do our best. So please support us, listen to the new song!
Yeah! And with that, I think we can gather together, right?
Together! Huddle, huddle, huddle, huddle... You guys ready? Here we go!
Mori, Calliope, Takanashi Kiara, Ninomae Ina'nis, Gawr Gura, Watson Amelia!
Together, we're...
Myth!
we're ready to greet the world!
we're voyaging forward with courage to run toward a brand-new start
let's go live!
bridging the distance across the sea endlessly
cheerfully meeting heart-to-heart!
waking from a dream, swept up into a stream, i make a wish and wait for my cue
how will we connect in this new frontier we're journeying through?
thriving in a scene where no one's ever been with vibrant colors bursting like stars
radiant and warm; charged with energy that's carried us this far
each new debut brings a miracle to life, surely we've gotta take that chance
we're running nonstop; straight to the top, that's right!
we're ready to change the game, a shimmering showcase creating a new place where we can shine!
day by day, sparkling stories will intertwine
get ready to cross the waves, we're voyaging forward with courage
to run toward a brand-new stage, let's go live!
bridging the distance across the sea endlessly, follow me
and we'll turn the page!
breaking through the doubt, we know we'll figure out a way to clear each towering trial;
sharing all our hopes, we can conquer any challenge with a smile!
we'll link our hearts as we search across the globe knowing
no matter where we are, no matter how far we can be stars, let's go!
i wanna chase a wish unwaveringly, playing out a grand story
share the futures that we can see, making them reality!
take my hand and reach for the screen
all we need are glittering dreams
our hearts and souls, all fulfilled in the world we build!
we're ready to seize the day, traversing the pathways, discovering highways to everywhere!
step by step, gathering stories that we can share!
get ready to lead the way with each generation, a shining sensation; a dream unfurls - let's make friends,
making a moment of history joyfully, follow me; we'll connect the world!
they'll hear our song ringing out over hills and oceans, our legend grows and continues!
we'll carry on starting now; setting hearts in motion - connecting all of the world!
Carry on,
starting now,
setting hearts in motion,
connecting all of the world!
Yaaay! Kikkeli-ki, everyone!
Did you enjoy the hololive English -Myth- 4th Anniversary Live? The show goes on!
I know it's hard to say goodbye, but before we go, we have some awesome merch to show you!
First up, we have this, the Acrylic Block.
The illustration theme is Broadway musical x retro outfits, perfectly fitting for our live show.
And it was drawn by the amazing Aki Akane-sensei!
It's a two-layer design, giving it a nice depth.
The thick acrylic makes it look great just as it is!
All right, on to the next one.
Next, we have Collection Cards!
These cards have a special touch with a translucent material and foil stamping, making them feel extra festive!
Each of us in Myth has our own card, so be sure to collect them all!
All right, next up.
And let's see... Oh, we got mini mascot plushies!
Each Myth member's mascot is turned into a cute plushie!
But this time, they're all dressed up with hats and ribbons to match the live show.
How cute! And you can attach them to your bag and take them anywhere you want.
Let 'em see the world!
Okay, what do we got next?
Next up is the Crossbody Bag. It's a simple, everyday-use bum bag.
The inside design features Myth's motif icons, making it super stylish!
Perfect for carrying the keychains around when you go out.
Thanks, or should I say, tankyuverymuch, everyone!
I sure feel like I want to collect them, and I hope you do the same.
And last but not least, thank you so much for supporting hololive English -Myth-!
Come catch us at the next show or stream!
OtsuMyth!